Mean any American United.
Happy I know you think
of. Where director. Being
close to the podium just
a moment I've typed you on the
thank you for the just the body of
a letter of the. Following
at least Tom hi skinny. Well
may see this. Guy Tell me is
a lot of the universe
to me it's usually in
a bad humor something of the still of the
crown jewel shall we have now I'll go my
own boss to be sure that of late he'll be
back in ten minutes if you can minutes or
time to be away from. US If you say.
Come off. OK I just said to you the ten
minutes of the last shine of the oil from
the edge of the first and I like it that
I have to to say. And I can stand being
spoiled little the gentleman I'm going to
see give him and I'm spoiling my to spoil
him just once sure I don't want to go in
with you No no I can handle things get
rough remember I'm here I've come
around and. Well you know how I hope
you'll come back oh you are
a very you know I. Love it just how fast
the love lawn by my pet the cat can take
in their own for
a while it was like you know
what I am. Around the. Room
or around Chan Bush. When you want
your ex-wife does he want to see you.
Oh no they don't know all
I only. Hello a house
a big slot machine KING Oh I ain't doing
that no more I'm retarded you know what I
mean so you want to visit Obama held on
nothing listen we're going to business I
thought you ought to know that the governor
didn't sign that reprieve and tomorrow
morning our Williams dies may just agronomist.
What he got to go get the governor
on the phone I can't one I can't locate he
was out fishing How many places to fish
out of it at least to the Atlantic and
Pacific either simplifies it as we don't
have
a phone and tell me what I had he's thinking.
Time of year reprieve or Williams will
support him for Senator Tom in the morning
post I'll be behind him up line and
sinker but you can do what
I know because we've been
a Democratic paper for over twenty years
all right after we get the reprieve where
we democratic or get all the unfair for
you get going remember the Morning Post
expect something should be done with
us today and you'll be you know you're
a boy. If
he is still added the first time I ever
double crossed the governor or can I do for
you Would you mind if I
sat down there's been
a lamp burning in the window for you
on here oh I jumped out that window
a long time ago. Oh ma'am one of those.
Yeah and that I can't.
How long is it how long it's what you know
work how long is this We've seen each
other oh oh let's see I spent six
weeks in Reno them to know about four
months again seems like yesterday to me
maybe it was yesterday do you been seeing
me in your dreams now doesn't dream about
you anymore while you would know the old
bill now yes I would I know you any time
any place in any way of repeating itself
or that's the speech you made the night you
propose I know that you still remember
it because I remember I didn't remember
it I would have the voice you hear so I
wish you hadn't done that really rock
divorced me thank you from the lose all faith
in them so. Almost give them
a feeling it was and want to let
you know that's what divorce is
a follow up nonsense you've got an old
fashioned idea the voice of somebody would
last forever till death do us part why
their voice doesn't mean anything nowadays
really just
a few words moment over here by Judge we've
got something between us nothing can
change. You know right now lay low don't
write I am fond of you you know you
know girl I often wish you weren't such
a stinker. Let in I suppose you must come
up meet my mother if you'd like but I am
ready to promise not to fight the divorce
and do everything you possibly could to
gum up the whole works I meant to let you
go it will be but you know it is you
never miss the water till the well runs dry
big bad luck things like you hiring an
airplane to right field Don't be hasty
remember my dear. They laid out of us twenty
minutes while the judge went out to watch
it I don't want to break but I've still
got the demo and in the same place
look you know the only I did not get
a husband I didn't want to see his home
broken home one home don't you remember the
home I promised to do that was the one we
were to have right after the honeymoon.
Was it my fault did I know that Coleman
was going to have another cave in I
intended to be with you on the moon it
will be honest I did all I know is that
instead of two weeks in Atlantic City
with my bride realized two weeks in
a coal mine with John crops you don't deny
that do you want to know I've proud of
it we'd be whole country on that story
as we did that is what I got married for
what is there now well but I came up here
to tell you is that you must have known
me a dozen times
a day sending me twenty telegram rather
beautiful telegram don't I everybody says
are you going to listen to what
I have to say when I see you as
a fighter you know the I'll tell you what
to do if you come back to work on the
paper if you find we can't get along
a friendly fashion we'll get married again.
Well sadly I have any hard feelings.
Some sort of way now would you please be
quiet just long enough for me to tell you
what I came up with to say
that for months and I have
a life state already I cannot write you
can you hold your hands on me when you
playing osteopathic ten but I'll listen
while you are no longer my husband and no
longer my boss and you're not going to be
my boss that's opposed to me just what I
say I mean you're not coming back to work
on the paper right Mr Bliss for the first
time today. Got
a better offer that I got of that all right
go on take your word for something else
that's the gratitude I get I
was handing out five years ago
a little college girl from
a school journalism I took
a doll face to take but it wouldn't take
me if I hadn't been so why should I still
be a nobody ever face around here Meg
again but I'm sure the reason was I made
a great report to you which one we have
is going to be on the paper and you know
everyone is here and I don't I and I can't
tell what irony and America are going to
listen to the pay this guy have to get along
without me so you just didn't work out
. It will work out if you'd be satisfied
with just being editor and reporter but
not you you had to marry me spoil everything
I wasn't. I suppose I proposed to you
well your friend if you did making goo goo
eyes at me for two years until I broke
down Walter and I still claim I was tight
that not a proposed deal of you to be
a gentleman you forgot all about it but
not sure. It was your use of we had
a bit of that alone what.
We're going to do for. Quite
a minute I'm actually I'm Guffey license
where you going to tell me not to day of
all days what's the matter with you were
you loony jumping to all this is really
this is no time. Oh Ron I suppose
oh yeah I have to you have to
be had to be like that everything happens
to me three hundred sixty five days
a year and this has to be the day plus I'm
out of all Sweeney dad I'm just as well
be the only man on the table they're
going to fix that they don't have
a baby they didn't do it on purpose
didn't I don't care we're doing all the
supposed recovering the Williams case
and where is it walking up and down the
hospital is and no sense of honor in this
country but well and you've got anybody
else. Who's nobody else on the
face of the right there's
a break for me and I feel that well you
know you're going to have just and I'll
likely get going down here on this
NG No I please state OK that's
a pretty frank you're going to get just the
way we use that fate I'm afraid of any
time any place anywhere don't mock me this
is bigger than anything ever happened to
watch don't go for me do it for the paper
grandstand gallant you won't do it for
love about money forget the other operation
twenty five functions with me you great
big bubble had not been able to earn five
bucks not to send more you wanna listen
Well good grief how much not on the paper
going to pay you there isn't any fall in
that case
a raise and off you go but you're all sham
I am your money that's trying to blank
check me honestly I'm sure it's
a remake of the how did you know it's an
engagement ring you tried to tell right
away that you would start reminiscing.
I'm getting married well and I'm also
getting his far away from the newspaper
business is I can get on. And throw him
out or you want to believe that you can
quit the newspaper business oh on up I know
you're only on
a war footing with me do you know what it
may not kill you you can't sell me that
all of those shows are good you're
a newspaper man that's why I'm quitting
I want to go someplace where I can be
a woman to be a trader I try to return
to watch regular journalism you're
a journalist Hilda and journalist how
does that mean peeking through keyholes
chasing after fire engines waking people
up in the middle when I asked them if it
was going to stop another war stealing
pictures off the ladies and all about
reporters will a lot of dancing but
it's kids running around without
a nickel in their pockets and what's on it
had those moments why don't know what's
going on why not. What's the use for
you you would know what it means to
want to be respectable and live
a halfway normal life the
point is I'm through with
you meet this man for me to return
please tell him to call rich makes five
thousand
a year but his learning is in the insurance
business insurance business and well
that's
a good honest business there's no more
slack for use on his own so adventurous
romance those for me with the I can't
think she'll be surrounded by policies
policies that my grandpa right hand and I
like it for small Besides he forgets the
office when he's with me he doesn't treat
me like an errand boy either Walter
treats me like a woman does doesn't
know that I treat you like
a water buffalo I don't know from one of
our fellows but I do know about him and
he's sweet nice considering he wants
a home and children so as mine are gone I
want to marry what is going to. Fall in
groups full of them well we've
both been born arguable we want
a horse thief in Mississippi couldn't be
the same for to get out talking about them
and I'm marrying tomorrow to
morrow for some reason I.
Well at last I got what I came
up in to tell you. Yes there is
a name one of the story so long
although so long only and that
elected next time you. Hear me.
Kind of took
a window and I said. Look I mean I just
want to wish you everything I couldn't give
him thank you on. This on the
phone when I started to get
a chance to see him more in this particular
book and my wife Mary. Where is it.
Right on the top waiting on the out
there. To run from me didn't. Know all it
wouldn't do any good Bono not afraid are
you afraid of course not well they come
home and see this paragon is going to as
you say I can bet on that what was it with
you and I got me thinking. Oh I
am sorry really I suppose Bruce
and I fall then fall with you
always go if somebody with
a lady takes its own I am sorry so many
folks for the lady he waits problem oh well
in that case. I doubt.
I can see right away my wife we've got the
right husband for you there is so much
me shall mistake I'm already married
already married. Oh Bill you should have
told me so hard Congratulations again Mr
Bobbitt Oh no Michelle My name's gives me
well I'm terribly busy just leave your card
with the boy what he said was the most
a brand name each of burns some of the
time I'm busy with Mr Bruce Baldwin here I
didn't hear what you said
that I was going to do
a good man you know what is it with you I
mind can all see that oh your goofball
Yes Who is he oh you're my name's Pete
Dame ish Mr Davis is this any concern of
yours oh well from now on I thank you for
keeping those out of my fish and then you
have again it's all just
a ball when I'm terribly sorry
about this mistake this is indeed
a pleasure. Oh that's wrong. Well because
you see I thought you don't mind if I
call your proved to you after all we're
proud to be related all too often you see
my wife that is your wife I mean really
oh you know you know you let me to expect
you're marrying
a much older man all right and what I say
they all want I don't worry about it I
realize you mean old in years. But you
always carry an umbrella Bruce looked
a little cloudy this morning that's
right I was too I hope. And of boy
a man ought to be prepared for any emergency
Well adding to that of the running
a lot yes we'd better be going where we
going I'm taking you to lunch didn't you
tell him how do you know if you didn't well
I guess he just wanted to surprise you
Bruce after you. Do you hear
they are wasting time on him but
a good nor the one who had
to do it glad to do it.
WELL AS WELL DON'T TELL ME until it's not
how things are then I can't complain I
can I'm hungry give me
a roast beef sandwich they're all white
and white bread guy over there to start
right in your building Oh I have the same
I guess you say yes that's how I play
bring some mustard to Gus Yes. Now
how how how. You going to get
a man in. The field Rosie is awful good.
You're getting very little girl she is I
realize that things have been different
for me ever since I met Ellie I've never
met anyone quite like her before everybody
else I've ever known well you're going
to always tell ahead of time what they're
going to say or do but not like that you
can't tell that about her that's nice.
You're getting something else to Bush you
getting a great newspaper man you know
it's all there on the best I have
a new side to see her go the Giants are you
know they had like to believe you meant
that and I do mean that listen if you ever
want to come by the newspaper bit weird
child. Well in spite of everything if I
ever do there's only one man I'd look for
in life I kill you I've never worked for
anybody and I hear that phrase that's my
diploma I must be quite
a business of it's. You sure you want to
quit now Bruce what do you mean what I
mean if there's any doubt about it or if
there's anything that you know this is
your chance to have a home
and to be like you said
a human being I'm going to make it take
that chance you know why I wouldn't let it
stay. She deserves all this happened it's
because all the things I couldn't give it
here all she ever wanted was
a home but I'll certainly try to give her
one I know you will where you can live in
harmony Albany and got
a family up and are just my mother she said.
Oh you've got to live with your mother
well just for the first year of
them will be nice yes there's
a home with mother in Albany too many nice
little town Albany they've got the state
capital A Yeah I know yeah
we've been there once.
This Were you ever forget the night you
brought the Governor Blanco down you see. I
was in taking
a bath when I came walking out what up.
She didn't know I was in town well
a Bruce how is business out there
any better well I'll bet he's
a mighty good insurance town most people
they take it out pretty early in life and
I can see why they would have to stick
show that most of our problems roofs I'm
going to feed me I ought to have taken
out of the insurance cause that really
doesn't matter no the and I and well you
know we. Does it but does it when you can
say stupid that it might have been
a good idea if we if I had taken on the
issue of well I mean honestly feel that
yeah I figure I'm in one business it really
helps you know course we don't help you
much while you're alive but after what
that's what counts. I don't get it.
And I should go I am so sorry I guess my
thought must have slipped Oh that's all
right would you like to drink coffee just
so we put some room in the car but it's
a nasty to show me to ask please and you
sent it out for me thanks Bruce have
a know I have
a lot to do this afternoon by the tickets
and check the baggage but do it tomorrow
this pony was way leaving
a park popped it in the sleep of Albany
Oh you. You're leaving Today at four
o'clock. And it's only two hours and it
doesn't give us much time and that all I've
got
a lot to do I want to get on with it then
the next three all down I will my front
tire that's nothing new here no never mind
I think I've got to do something about
the. Copy to the telephone since I came
back to the table I'm sure things does it
fine thanks I'm. Terribly sorry about
this so listen Bruce I want to get that
straight I musta misunderstood you you mean
you're taking the sleep for the day and
then getting married tomorrow oh my crown
oh what he said like oh Paul all to hell
toss and turn all night past you better
tell em mama is coming along to the mother
or your mother kick the bucket I bother my
mother or your mower well that relieves
my mind was growling let yourself out
that way is more sweet always wanting to
protect me and I meant I wasn't much of
a husband but you can
always count on me of
a woman that she don't need you very
much Mr Burns I aim to do most of the
protecting myself to Verne's
telephone for me that's
a strange con man. You know only
he's not such
a bad fellow you know he should make some
girl real happy I'm happy he's not the
man for you I can see that but
you sort of like him he's got
a lot of charm and he comes back
naturally his grandfather was
a snake. Oh definitely this is any way we
can stop the four o'clock train to open
you from leaving town I think
complete. Maybe we could finally get
this get all this we need to send him out
of town on the two weeks vacation on the
way over I keep it sure I don't feel this
coming back though she doesn't really get
that I probably should she stay here and
listen don't we just agree on the obvious
I mean even goodbye. This
is bad business for us the
net of all the Earl Williams case for years
I've been reading about. What is the
lowdown on it oh simple funny for one of
those who lost his job and went and shot
a cop and was coming out through to quieten
down now they're going to hang him
tomorrow you're shaper of you've been taking
you signed him when he was out of his
mind he did it why doesn't the state
just put him away because it had to be
a coming policeman you know what I mean
to leave. The colored vote very important
in this town especially when the election
coming up tonight on A and it hang his
own grandmother be reelected I should think
you could just show that the man wasn't
responsible is not so easy maybe it isn't
so hard either why would immediately but
now they have to have another expert examine
him before they hang him Bernie Madoff
is going to do it you say the same as all
the rest suppose he does let's just keep
nearly all of you getting to do with
all Williamson print and a half
a statement and I long side of it you know
double columns run your interview and in
a sense the same interview shows he's guilty
no you know the you can do it you can
say that poor devils like you could I'm.
Not going away I think on how long with
the interview take oh about an hour for
the interview another hour to write and
that's when I filled it we could take
the six o'clock train if it save
a man's life no booze if you want to savor
William's life you write the interview
yourself you're still
a good reporter he'll be you know I
can write that kind of thing it takes
a woman's touch and he sat down yet I think
well thank you at Sweeney's the best
man you've got on the paper for that's
offices to stuff because we need stuff he
just told me his wife finally had twins.
In the terrible place we want to set up
right now we can't find him anymore so we
as twins and everybody and you guys hang
them are now Waller Look it isn't what you
argue with you argue with it otherwise
you're going on
a honeymoon with blood on your hands how
can you have any avenues after that all
through the years you'll remember that
a man went to the gallows because she was
too selfish to wait two hours I tell you
a bruise or
a woman's face or come between you on the
train tonight not the prettiest on all
the rest of your I. Hope based on the oh
you want what. I just remember it's me was
only married four months ago. Back to.
You when I'm licked you know Mr Sweeney
didn't have twenty. In the window Wallace
all is it was nothing well come on this
we're going to you know we're starving
again and I'll offer you to
a business probably not interested but
you'll be interested now you are smarter
than many of those I know
a mold problem way and he made me want to
talk to him like Bruce you persuaded me
to do the story you can write and I spent
insurance policy for me when he said no
no no no no come our star I would use my
wife for business for when I'm in the
Bruce Well that having
a policy oh twenty five fifty
thousand bucks the commission on
a hundred thousand dollar policy around
a thousand dollars but I go through all of
the thousand dollars I couldn't use that
money Bruce how long would it take
to get him examined so I could get
a company doctor here in twenty minutes
but I don't like you I Got It All right
Bruce suppose you have Mr Burns examined
over in his office and see what they'll
allow on that old caucus of his if his
Hey I'm better than I was I was never
anything to brag about now the pros I go
back and change and dress and after you
get the check you phone me I'll be in
the press room in the criminal courts
building one of them one by the way I
think you better make that essential fact
check or do you think I am
a crook Yes I know said if I check no star
you get me it will be said if I want my
fingerprints how Thanks I still got those
guys how much do I owe you. Thank you.
Bruce I'm sorry sorry but you know everything
five hundred fifty five when I take
it I take anybody I know what I'm
doing. Something I don't cap and I know
a lot of people who never did anything
clean up all the things piece to. Remember
it's everything we. All really you know
change and turn I just about I mean don't
you Bruce I just gave everything I had to
go they all got left on some of them I'm
a sign of. From the way to.
Come on. I'm trying
I mean yesterday right Willcox three four
hundred I meant to. Say take I want to
burst What are you a doing or
e to ones with him what's the matter
with you guys crippled or something.
Press room honestly I mean it was
a little Sergeant you talking although I
was young. And I know I told you this
a pressure on the criminal
courts building Jake
a new lead on the hanging this alien This
from New York Dr Max Jr how for. Yeah
he's going to interview with me in about
half an hour in the sheriff's office must
be about the tenth dailiness they put on
Williams if he wasn't crazy We've already
would be by the time ten of those babies
got through psychoanalyzing and given the
desk there's this guy I go home from
a good get out for yourself is the guy
they sent to Washington to interview the
brain trust he said they were saying that
number appears the situation on the eve
of the hanging out there couple of approach
this is Murphy more slop on the hanging
a double guard has been thrown around the
jail municipal buildings railroad term
loans and elevated stations to prepare for
the expected general uprising of radical
right and the hour of the execution Sheriff
I just put two hundred more relatives
on the payroll to protect the city from
the Red Army which is leaving Moscow in
a couple of minutes the real red menace
shows up the sheriff will still be crowing
Well when you've got that good sure looks
good from here Well hello everybody got
back I and I you know they glad to see it
you know when you get to have Madoff like
that right over now it's just
a farewell appearance I'm going to Disney
for myself and what you know I'm getting
married tomorrow I want I want you here I'm
going to meet him and I we're going to
the wedding ring and I
might use you for Branson
a growing Oh how I heard him Dooley you
get married for you know the man I'd you
know be honest are you know feeling like I
got in here three tickets to Albany and
six o'clock train tonight do you mean three
but me and my bro and hats off boys his
sweet darling all that's going to marry
is really going to be all right I'm going
to set. And out and through the newspaper
business and your picture here this thing
alone and hanging out and that's not very
wise over the back fence is not agreeing
with that because if she gets to be you
really are going to be here I don't.
Understand Jefferson is never that simple
school is this time of day where you care
you quit said you were thrilled
just thought it might be
a good plan itself. I was just
practicing for the Williams party I'm on
a mission I was hanging guilty not
interested I'll go right down.
And keep quiet down there I don't
expect this to get any worse than.
Respect for the press around here. Says
anybody follow me around I know right
General de held
a lot I know you're going to marry just had
lunch with them you know your question
yes I tell them any more questions I'm going
to let you do it really I haven't got
time to do any on them WILLIAMS If you
know what he was doing when he fired their
gun Yes Gus no yes the state you know if
the answer is yes who is he was he do he
was a bookkeeper he started twenty dollars
a week and after fourteen years he grabs
the words from south up to seven hundred
fifty from Markham no McClatchy Company
goes out of business and Williams loses job
Dima can't get another. So he starts
hanging around the park wasn't
a lot of so far as making fun of speeches
because believe and make some of his own
up or done. Anything else dark you know
a little bit about almost everything OK you
have nothing to worry about drugs. Are
you doing Bruce there's just one more thing
Mr Burns just like Mr Burns most of all
right our thanks very much Doc who is
a beneficiary excuse me excuse me but I was
curious of your death who do we pay the
money to liability of cars. I don't know
but it makes me feel pretty funny Oh now
why shouldn't I make you only my whatever
it was you know I feel I should take care
that you will take care of her brood
thinking of the doctor's right I'm good for
a long time yet Look Bruce this is
a debt of honor with me I was out bad
husband day old a chicken to clean
a lot of alimony if she wanted to but she
wouldn't take any she had it coming to
her but she was too independent Well I'm
a dependent Oh you are Bruce I know you are
but no you just figure it this way I'm
good for well with say these twenty
five years yet well by that time you'll
probably have made enough so the money
won't mean anything to you but suppose you
have made good Bruce what about his old
age think of Hilda. I can see her now
white head lavender and Old Lace Can't
you see her BRUCE Yes yes I can she's
old isn't she proofs don't you think
that it was entitle to spend her last
remaining years without worries of money
of course you do approve of course of your
point of fact. And remember I love her
too. And some beginning to realize
that the beauty of it is she'll never
have to know until I've passed on.
Maybe she'll think kindly
of me after I'm gone.
She.
Makes me feel like he'll come between us
no no Bruce you didn't come between us it
was all over for her before
you came on the scene for me
a water it'll never be what you want and
I say your minute please. Excuse me
Bruce. If you're going to get more
efficient than you're sort of I'm sure
of both water that's for twenty five
hundred dollars. Well there is here we are
certified everything by. Gosh. I'm afraid
you will feel ashamed to think she hasn't
trusted you but you know someday. Old Ruth
you promised to phone or since you got
oh yes yes of course. I mean you're the
Johnson press room criminal records
building the numbers are
you offering to get
a phone thank you. Give me love
you oh yes our way thank you.
Write our really Guard thank you.
Jasim speaking of blue Oh Hello Ruth
I got
a dime I want to know you have been playing
for an hour and I have the one you.
Love or those that you can check this is
how to find certified and everything I
would write my pocket and
your packing that went
a bit maybe it isn't so fine Bruce Where
are you going Mr Burns offers T.V.
. On our Look Bruce I want you to carry
the check around in your pocket well
because the kids Yes I know all that
but to Bruce is an old newspaper
superstition that the first big check you
get you put in the lining of your hat in
your hat. It brings good luck I've been
a reporter for twenty years and I've heard
that before that I know it sounds silly
dear but do it for me please
for yes yes right now just
a minute. They
are I've done it anything
else oh yes all right
ah. Yes Yes I'm telling you by now everything
all right Bruce Oh yes you'll be sure
to tell if you get right to work fine Oh
I must be going out Oh Oh Bruce don't
forget this my right no right oh you don't
want to I don't show you I DO YOU HAVE
NO NO NO our thanks for everything you
mean when you say I said thanks for
everything nonsense Don't thank
me I should thank you song so on.
Oh really well you know around here I know
they do they're all Williams Now bottle
service no more interview out sheriff's
orders sides doctors coming over to do it
all so is no money why don't think of that
about yeah just maybe I was allowed to
talk about the Mary Jo open up
here that you really don't have
a lot. Lower.
Than it down for
a lot of adoptive human No I haven't
anything else to do right. Now
so used to I couldn't plead insanity
because I'm just as soon as anybody else
didn't mean to kill that policeman course
and I was against everything I've ever
stood for and you know what was in the
accident I'm not guilty it's it's just the
world see what you mean sorry about the
lipstick curl I looked after you lost your
job what do I try to find another job I
mean how do you spend your time or used to
sit around the park any place well I don't
smoke when you're in the park to hear
any of those speeches you mean as well as
to talk too much Yeah well I didn't pay
any attention you see I was here anything.
Yes you serious thing you remember
anything in particular when I was one
fellow he will talk about he talked about
production for use protection for you as
he said everything should be made use of
he's quite a bit of sense doesn't
mean yes I like him he was
a good speaker. When you found
yourself with a gun in your hand and
a policeman coming at you. But if you
think about it I don't know exactly what
a something could have been production
for use I don't know why with
a gun for
a gun. To shoot of course Oh and maybe
that's why I used to be neat seems
reasonable yes yesterday but you
see I've never had a kind of
a hand before and that's what
a gun is for isn't it maybe that's why yes
that's what I thought of production for
you it simply isn't there he said
there's nothing crazy about that as
a whole I think you know you write about
that in your paper what you think that I
would you say to the
rest this morning she's
a wonderful better sixty years she's beautiful
isn't she and I was up you know that
I. Had soft I like talking
to your environment because.
The barrel. Good luck. Three landladies
four and welded I wonder what the pros
going to do with artillery used for is one
of the runs along the Gulf then what he
did in Belfast when he wanted to go to
Hollywood and I'm thrown in jail for
arson largely is that if you have
a mission change and back. Your stairway
Sam would you mind turn on some lights
it's
a dark you can see. You're right was this
guy girl is going to marry I don't know
if something I get the
marriage six months or
a life or she will be able stay away from
the paper any longer than that did you
see it when I bear one off. That it must
be pretty nice to be able to walk out of
a place with. A publicity job offer to me
last year should have taken it so that
I'd like a job on the skin is to
not go for it I wouldn't mind
a nice big loan with
a. Ten The one I don't I should munch
she just like I was for we wouldn't be
sticking around waiting for
that guy well Mr Malim
a lawyer the wife of my Asterix have
been looking for your train some to call
Williams or any first record year of every
Iceman She rose that you sent her what
you want done with them
tomorrow morning and
a lot of wise guys ain't you you're breaking
up the game all they want you won and
I came to it. I came to tell you what I
think of your folly if you're short on him
he was worth breaking my nails on I take
your face wide open Yes horrible sweet
heart was going to swell story we give you
now will you what crimes are now going
to pull out of me long enough for me but I
never said I love DARYL WILLIAMS It was
wonder marry him on the gallows
Kim A got out and about my being
a soulmate and having
a love nest where the more you do that
you've been sticking around then cuckoo ever
since they threw in the house no one
everybody knows your girlfriend I met Mr
Williams just once in my life too when he
was wandering around in the rain without
his hat and coat on like
a sick dog the day before the shooting to
me why I went up to him like any human
being and work through and I asked him
what was the matter and he told me about
being fired after being on the same job
of fourteen years in birth. And I brought
him up to my room because
there was one day I'll put on
a phonograph on listen to him please. I did
and he just sat there talking to me all
night he never once laid
a handle on me and and in the morning he
went away and I never saw him again till
that day of the trial. Yet I was let in
what I went to this day that's why you
visit kill me because you will give us three
to make they said no not like that and
of all I did at the press room were why
don't you go see your boy he's got
a nice room you won't have it long enough
to call over seven am The wonder of the
life and oh god that is
a good idea all. Well
said her version of
a painting the night for your
boyfriend. Shame on you shame on you.
Oh poor little fellow that never met nobody
no harm but never this minute with the
angel of death beside him I knew all right
now what you're going to get out of me I
don't want that ARE THEY COME ON Molly let's
get out on me you know when I KNOW THE
NEWSPAPER MAN I'll even though it is long
and OH MY GOD I'M LAUGHING Oh my God I
would roll my eyes and
tell me why I was. Doing.
And I know you're just
an honor to be back in
a minute. Guys with twenty more current
rights to use like you know you.
Gentlemen of the press
you know me long for
you know oh hell no Bruce
Well where are you
your where when how did that happen
in my name and I'll be right back.
Oh I'm sorry. If I don't
I shan't hurt my back
what's going on around here I was in trouble
I mean I wish to defend my hand from
your tank you my mother was the one I
know her still give married six months I
don't know what you fellows are talking
about what do you want. Oh I got the
tickets for the hanging here boys may not
be white Can't you hang this guy's five
o'clock instead of you I won't hurt you
we can make the city edition oh no that's
that's kind of roll Roy After all I can't
hang a man in the sleep just to please
a newspaper you know but you can reprieve
him twice oh no use three days before
election can't you know you can run on our
ticket you can do that all right honest
boys I had absolutely nothing to do with
those reprise how do we know there won't
be another reprieve
tonight what if there's
a go over upon the whims and say well you
won't find him insane because he isn't
he's just the same as I am Santa. Oh and
I'll be serious but after all this is
a hanging and it's going to go according
to schedule seven o'clock in the morning
and not a minute earlier
after all and such
a thing is being humane and all right I
think the way you want to favor and please
don't call me Pinky because I got
a name see and it's Peter B.
Hart Well what's that before. When I am
innocent I didn't do anything I never stole
our watch and mine where you didn't loose
I know you didn't All right Mike and I
let him out I can't believe he's accused
of stealing a watch and they found
a watch on now I never stole Ruth and who
accused him damn of the way the biggest
crock and I know it's all good and I know
you really mean not to let him out or on
to know I never saw Morris please. Well
actually that I read the post in the
morning I can't imagine
a door thing like that to me I can't think
of any enemies I am sure you haven't any
good enough to take and we have it right
here. That's a funny superstition you're
a newspaper people have this business.
About being arrested at first I thought
maybe water burns might have something to
do with it but then of course I realized
he couldn't provide for his or very much
for I feel that all four years I found
that it was murder I've lost my watch yes
that I'm well but Bruce never mind I have
the money you got to give me
a check to that picture of us and drug you
don't bother Bruce you'll find lots of
things with. No price do you wait
here I'm not taking any more chances
I'll be down three minutes meeting and
explain. And so into this little tortured
mind came the idea that that gun had been
produced for use and use it he did but
the state has a production for use planned
to it has a gallows and at seven am
a Muslim miracle occurs that gathers will
be used to separate the sort of girl
loose from his body and out of mommy Malloy's
life will go the one kindly soul she
ever knew that's as far as she got. But
I ask you guys can that girl write an
interview she'll doodle somebody else comes
along I don't feel very ethical reading
other people's already you get that ethics
down you're the only one who swiped any
of it I still say that anybody can write
like that I mean going to give it up
permanently the so sorry for the guy in
the insurance business now I give that
marriage three months and I'm like I'm
free to want any takers I got that he was
getting so dark I leave the
room not being discussed by
a bunch of old ladies I'll
post again we want to present
a place where I don't get sore early we
were only Santas well reported like you
wouldn't want C.C.
This silly thousand like
that all right without
a single quiver I want to live like
a human being that like you chaps that you
all are well I've got some news for you
yes yes I got the interview all right
but I've got some more important news
impression I got
a pencil and take it down already. Now
get this you double crossing chimpanzee
there ain't going to be any of you and I'm
going to be the story and that's what if
I chicken US is leaving with me in twenty
minutes I wouldn't cover the burning of
Rome fuel they were just lighting it up
if I really my two eyes on you again I'm
going to walk right up you want to hammer
on that monkey skull of yours the rings
like
a Chinese gong Oh so you know why I'm angry
with you but pressure to get away to
tell you the story of his watch and there's
just one other little thing I want you
to listen to. Here that
that's the story I just wrote
Yes yes I know we had
a bargain I just thought I'd write it I
didn't say I would tear it up it's all in
little pieces now and I hope to do the same
for you know someday I have my friends
is my farewell to the newspaper
game I'm going to be
a woman out of this getting machine I'm
going to have babies and take care of them
and given the royal rights to grow and
and as I was the one of them look at
newspaper again I'm going to write my hand
oh. Oh Mr Barnes Yes she's telling her.
Another thing out of. His mind there
it is. I'm going after the story of
the nation was going to go right through
the voice of the newspapers they take up
so much of my time you know they wanted
me to hang Williams at their convenience
all I have told you everything what they
did to me and your garden but I believe
always after me great of you asked me to
of course I did rather promise to make
them some sort of sleep and when I
finished here you don't mind that's hardly
ethical doctor you see all statements are
supposed to come from me when you say to
give them some sort of joint interview I
can discuss some of the psychological
aspects of the case you know you mean we
have our pictures taken together. Because
I don't make
a very good picture all that doesn't matter
not to the pub visitors the main things
that I know are there I'm getting awfully
tired can I go back to jail again when
I'm awfully sorry I forgot you were
there no Mr Williams with some further
questions for you here if you want extinguishing
the life Lagos doctor saying we're
going to look at what we have to do
over here Mona Lisa. When it comes
you know of course that you're going
to be executed Now who do you feel is
responsible for that. I'm innocent
it wasn't my fault so there's
a postcard that I want to buy
a little right along and I will see you
again young woman next time you see me I
should be writing in
a Rolls Royce giving interviews on success
along you wage slaves wow you know when
you're calling
a fire escapes and getting kicked out of
front doors and eating Christmas dinners
and joints don't forget your pal Hill the
jobs they were in when the road goals of
the OK OK
OK let me to jailbreak
a book I would say look
you want to play
a lot. OK What was the hour
who didn't think it was
OK I'll tell her you're real disappointed
at Bankstown Williams just escape go by I
don't know you on the back would have gone
over the wall don't you think about the
cut OK. I'll post
a lot of words because just like
you. Well actually I am just
a kind of jail yeah yeah yeah
don't worry I'm on the job oh
shut. Up the
Alexandra.
Field. Thank you
Eleven. I
thank you our Kelli Arena thank you.
Then you have to rewrite. It here Hello
Gail here's the situation now ready
Williams was taken over to the sheriff's
private office to be examined by this
professor at Harvard and in
a few minutes he shot his way out you
know nobody knows where he got the gun he
went to stairs in the infirmary and got out
through the skylight He musta slid down
the drain pipe to the street no nobody
knows what we got what they do they will
talk of us we want you to describe commission
offers ten thousand dollars reward
for what you might be talking you know
clue yet as to when his whereabouts Oh no
there's
a little feature don't there's been an
accident about it to your mom yeah here
Obama criminals cry for I don't know looks
like I was laid off unexpectedly in the
hands of share of heart while bombing squads
went over the following deputies were
rushed to the hospital to find for any of
you their names are Marvin de Wilkerson
the mayor's brother in law after all I've
done for you our issues to the sheriff's
uncle on his mother's side Jim
highlights on stroke heart was man when
a man's doing
a sheriff's landlord and Lester Winthrop
who married the sheriff's niece you
remember the very homely thing hard to
write back this will rise age fifty five
scrub lady was scrubbing the floor the
calmest growing wish on the left like I want
to share
a heart was devotees if you look. There
goes another Scout Lady I was going to fly
from the to the hospital for you back when
he was speaking given the task it was to
make five and you don't know
how he escaped maybe half
a mile so we're going to vote for him no
mansion description of row Williams was
seen boarding a. Plane back home
but you go on also to. Get in
a lot of parents quick.
To. Pull over this.
Whole story and how we just got back an
escape and got it exclusive Yeah that's
right Ms Tippett cause me problems in fifty
bucks to tear it out of coolly Never
mind that was a story or just
a minute now given the story
that I'm telling you first I had
a good moment I had and it was exactly mine
I was Bush's man and I want it back. We
should moment short your show you'll get
to know what's the story so nobody write
down here I swear on my mother's
grave all right he says that wait
a minute your mother's alive my
grandmother great to go you know he was
a story when you get that money down
here. As you start the jailbreak of your
dreams it seems this expert back to the
heart of the profound think it from New
York was giving Williams A final sanity
test in the sheriff's office you know
sticking
a lot of pins in him so that he could get
his reflexes when he decided to reenact
the crime exactly as it's taking place
and how to study Williams's powers of
coronation Well I'm coming
to it cause he had to have
a gun to reenact the crime with and who
do you suppose applied it Peto the heart
will be for brains and. No good.
I tell you nothing I'm not good
enough to make this one up well the sheriff
is going to fasten the professor gave
it to you and I will shop has the right to
classify it no ads and perfect. In this
year of
a roll the red carpet along with it is an
umbrella it could've been more ideal Oh
oh no no and off it wasn't that they
didn't look out of hospital but they're
awfully afraid he'll recover Oh it's great
where you know they are stop worrying
about the money I see you get in fifteen
minutes Well I've got to get their fifteen
minutes this is downstairs waiting
in a taxi can't for me and we're in
a hurry all dominant eventually
to me there's a guy with me in
a taxi in front of the criminal courts
building is named Bruce full of it doesn't
look like they look like they're following
the movie rough but I know him going in
with her never thought don't you know what
a couple get go you only get about two
minutes every you know there are sort of you
waiting how much was it again four
hundred fifty dollars for just
a second believe me I need four hundred
fifty dollars worth of counterfeit money
game carry that much voice knowledge is
that four hundred fifty counterfeit we're
going to get it oh I got that on the go
this is what they go to building and I was
coming right over so to get overly nice
things for your story here and good luck on
your honeymoon Yeah no never mind
Thanks Jesse that might get you.
Oh hell are you still here now out in
Niagara Falls make you speaking a mom I got
a good feature for you on the man on
Friday Mrs Peabody Well basically one have
solid state speak I gave birth to
a pickaninny and patrol wagon with Chef
Hochul special right was quite I can use
nurses now from Phoebe was walking on the
street when I was by now so they close in
the patrol wagon start
a race with the start when the picaninny
was born the rifle squad examined it
carefully to see it was there
a Williams Well I know he's hiding somewhere
he used to say they named the kid
Peter Hart will do well that's where I'm
a share Yeah they all chip you know Rose
I thought you were downstairs and it was
on
a man on earth is another arrested again what
forces time and it was oh I call it mashing
your I didn't kill day
I was sitting right in
a taxi where you left me and
the young lady seemed to have
a disease spell and I just.
One of the she's kind of.
Yeah she's a blonde. Yes very blunt Never
mind I don't know what happened just
a minute. Getting home and parents telling
times if you pros where I am twenty
seven percent hold on I would have
lesser You know what I was there
a minute ago but I was. Looking
in. Double crossing Hello No not
to Bruce we can't get there right away
twenty minutes you see I have to wait for
the right to know what I see if I
hear you two hands again on what
a break it's only me Well Terry I know you
don't have any money they got in our A
sixty four said welcome to it thanks you
gotta buy an annuity on Saturday Mum No I
can't give you an official
statement oh wait a minute here's
a major maybe you'll give us one I've got
a statement there don't pester me now
please I've got my mind is on you say
anything everything Cheryl was hard to
tell your obviously there's so many
cockroaches around here I'm all in a
women have a statement you know we got
a present prime minister I can't help
that I've nothing to say and I don't this
time I just
a moment please what do you know about
the escape how to get out where to get
a gun when I'm going to bars myself
fashionistas they run the election and what
effect will always have on the voters
not I want to show our How can I not
avoidable misfortune like this have any
influence on the upright citizens of our
fair city Well Mr Mayor plays
there is there a red menace are
a thing I did with him to get out of rubber
jail ya you understand the gas you pick
out somebody to be responsive Is there any
truth in the report that your own style
means payroll Yeah the Saturday claims you
sleep around underway Never mind that
you know you don't forget I'm barely going
to come in fact I want to show I still
want to get away Hi How are you to get the
Grammy Award Higher Honor if they don't
on the right uprising tomorrow night
right up I'm going to be you know right
uprising they're going to says the situation
calls for the militia are going to be
really going to court make us saying
anything the governor says the potential of
a lie because there are stable government
or big crimes the mayor and those are
have shown themselves to be
a couple of eight year olds playing with
fire and yeah you can quote I'm as follows
It is
a lucky thing for this city. Next two views
and election is the sentence will thus
be same the expense of impeaching the mayor
and the share. A bag I used to see of
mayor excuse me boys I'm going
to my way let's not leave
a good engineer this little red
know what you mean he told him just
a minute not to tell you I've got to
locate it Williams where I'm going to be
pretty used to live I just got
a table I'm just a still he's
a rifle squad just going home. If you
are in the police state I want to hire
a good guy I've got so much to see here
from this big sheriff through through you
mean I'm through I mean I'm
scratching here and I want to take
a back story on how to Sherman your play
reform the read what I read I went into
the red and you know it there are
a lot of communistic sympathizers
around and I thought that if I got
a slogan like that I could but I had no art
but that's got nothing to do with this
case during
a lifetime to one of our lot at stake and
of our way here we don't have we're going
to lose and we're going to have
a young family and he can't get away when
you mean it can't get away get away get
any where you want I what do you want Are
you sure of heart while I'm here what is
it you're a hard man to find here I have
a message here from the governor uses
Actually it was really prefer Williams for
who will use reprieve and
you said there was not
a pyrrhic grave How do you know anything
about the rightness of me to think of what
I'd like to do to you who have who are they
when I gave it you know but he was out
fishing to get the governor on the phone
now he's not there he's out Doc she was on
the phone I read you have a
right decision come to shooting
a guy who has done nothing for the last
forty years but play P not get elected
governor right away think he's
a tiresome read that if you say nice things
when he knows very well Williams isn't
insane Well I never met the man you're
a pilot in the temporal room cement ship
pretty quickly got to think fast What are
we going to talk about how you're still
in this state on account of you know all
frayed you know as an afterthought Tom I
want your resignation now oh yes yes this
is my room where we're at holy month of
the wire and if they think that Williams
comes from out of the rifle squad have
other discounts on the whole phone call I
did hold the wire cover
a veteran camera and I'll. This huge
never arrived with this messiah I didn't
remember when I came through
that door and I thought he was
a sheriff are I mean you watch your salary
twenty dollars so cut me off I like to
make three hundred fifty dollars a month
that's almost two hundred dollars
a week I couldn't afford this
who do you think now I need
a fellow like you in the city sealers
office in the accident shooters you mean
actually were aware of it and I didn't come
around my wife would want me to do that
why not well you see my wife lives in the
country with my family I saw lots of them
bring around here we pay all the
expenses. I don't think I have
a section but I got two kids going to
school and if they change towns they lose
a grade they're not all that I want I'm
skeptical rate and I'm guaranteeing that
they will graduate high Hold your horses
a little Are you afraid I want to say this
we have that kind of peculiar hold all
it does now remember you never deliver this
yes I know I did and you got caught in
the traffic or something you know I came
around by accident tragic death now get
out of here and don't let anybody shade of
this but how do I know of the kind I see
me in my office tomorrow what's your name
Paddy but once you I've gone not really
on our own all you've got to do is to lay
low and keep your mouth shut I'm tired
Anyhow here go out of
this aggression nice home
a place that take good
care of you just tell
a friend sent you here sixteen dollars on
a car when you away don't some god I'm
telling one minute you forgot to tell we
want to see monish biomarkers it hard not
always you very well and it's going to
because my health is what my wife flower
effects sent to my wife affix anything
like that for
a regular stand on the all right I want to
show up to Kale why you are what I said
with
a reprieve Fred if I am doing as I tell it
all right hello some shoot to kill that's
the artist class I want to live on or dollars
award five hundred dollars to the man
who doesn't and I go right over.
I totally double crossing high
United another Don't get me get in this
is stuff that you promised of all of this
time who made us you and that albino of
yours talking about eventually none other
gentle albino will do the one comes along
right here in this country she tries
anything else you have to stay right here
and I don't want you to win or be on
a phony charge either to bring up money
oh yeah four hundred books four hundred
fifty H.
Can't blame a guy for trying to
give me a receipt like give you
a scar you got funnier than all and I'll
take Mr Baldwin's wallet to Mr Baldwin's
worth his price come on come on really
all right you'll be I'll do it for you
because I like you but you'd better tell
that financier to be more careful in these
hard times and I believe you're following
the character brass knuckles too I don't
talk this way to know that you're out
for another good at the station wait
a minute wait
a minute you'll take it over to the station
all right you'll take it to the twenty
seven precinct and telegraph how
this I haven't to have held
a bunch of having an albatross and I had
a bad idea. No wait. You
know operate a hell of
a chance when you can write that phone
never mind. You're not going to talking
about where I am. Going down or.
Should be you know I'm your friend remember
I'm going to write the story and the
production will be honest that's right
we're looking for you which you don't want
to hurt your friend don't move maybe
you're my friend and maybe you're not but
don't come any near you can't trust anybody
in this crazy world. I know where you
would just anybody you know do that put it
back put it back you know if you try any
tricks I'll shoot you I knew right from
here sure you could you know what to do.
You know how to kill me. You know you're
right Honey We're Killing the British so I
thought wait
a minute where you going. She is going to
close the door so nobody to see her you
know you were you were going to get somebody
but I don't want it or I want to be
left alone get your shoe while you're going
to master me again I won't let you do
let. Me give your sorrow assurance.
I'm awful tired or I couldn't go home let's
stop there no you're here I don't care
I'm not afraid to try and stop you knowing
the phone I'm going to him you're going
to be quiet waking me up in the middle
of night talking to me about things you
don't understand that are going to take
me back to some very real they will tell
you why I couldn't go through it I would
be right because if you think I could.
Give me one appearance
Quick tell me. Hello help.
Please and I said to be down trying to
some terrific has happened hold on when I
call the movie or read about my prosthesis
announcement everything well I guess I
don't always hear you right
the press room almost on
a level where I need to write those checks
in the US have to capture their whims
and all the rhetoric and how their own kind
of this process just runs ahead of the
problem right up front but I
realize. Always that oh oh.
Oh I'm all right I got to find her as
everybody and I hear them all go oh please
tell me where they've gone please tell me
Mommy I don't know how awfully busy my
mama look they got him surrounded
they're going to shoot him down like
a dog if you told your special guy OK OK
you got until you got I know for I got
a way out there that I want to send
a street set and forth oh that's where he
used to where you don't go all the time
in Maui right here. One way. Down
the pipe I didn't mean to shoot me really
I didn't. But. You don't you think
for me thanks just they
were beautiful so that's.
True for everything don't you just don't
want to keep him from going to it's crazy
really can't help but I think so think you
know I'm trying to take credit reports
let him take me when you have
to see. My who locked the door.
To let you know it is no it
is not good in this to come.
Out and I was told to
go to. Find out I am.
OK if I don't look at the beginning I am
exposed eventually after all we got some
phone calls today what you do not run not
necessarily It's also not something that
happened came up here and had hysterics
pretty sick I feel OK I don't feel so good
smart or I gotta do anything for you you
don't want to stick to me you didn't bump
in the way you did you ate you funny here
where is he not me alone when your own
kids give you the best you
are Mr Hello Jim there's
a false alarm they surrounded the house all
right but they forgot to tell Williams
and he wasn't saying oh we're going on
outside the whole police force turning on
a serial killer we'll let your guard the
way it was in my wallet when I came to me
Well John Williams You
know I've been talking
a good ass and years cause. I never been
so tired in my life why where Melrose
station are I can make me tell my how I am
all of them and hey fellows as those got
him back no lady just called to take to be
armed James Williams is hiding under her
piazza I'm going to stand up going up every
other place just want to go out if I
have to stick around I'll cover
this envoy and I spent about
a forty on taxi cab already I still have
no more going out never mind so I'm scared
officer I'll pull the shades down I did
there was no in those lines around.
You know if I got on to lead anywhere they've
been looking for might be right here
in this building something sure as you
are hanging around like a duck in
a shooting gallery because it's going to
get out of it and out of the reach the
ground I'm pretending there ain't any or
all of this roof it's only about four feet
and once we go to the roof it is five down
a great price and coming at it one of these
windows on this side of the story is
going to walk right in the wind and that's
demands at work why don't you boys go
home made Williams the coming call on you
know going to be fun if you do in this
building somewhere why not
such a building everybody take
a fall and I'm not going to
want to go out of this with
a great bunch of reporters you are the
biggest star in two years you're all too
lazy to go out say earlier if I know you
you seem pretty high just to get rid of
a few kind of scoop was something I didn't
know my own has been given to the story
on how Williams got the gun that you smuggler
going to what is my life I know I did
not think I'm playing my own opinion that
my girl alone she said Will. Spondon
mother don't try and Mother me playing cat
and mouse with my poor boy keeping him
locked up like making
a train to you supposed to be married
tomorrow I'll be with you in five men who
don't have to go with me at all just give
me Bruce's money and stay here forever as
far as I'm concerned for the other players
or you'll call I sat right around these
men if they all looked like murderers to
me when I go but murdered and you have yet
to talk about any such thing I'm hoping my
son that he has never lied to me when I
was very surprised I never said anything
like that do you know I didn't I said I
was that trying to find I was not at all
balled up can't you see that you all and I
give him the job I mean clearly we all want
to I don't know where I hear that stuff
and what do you ask her for she don't know
where he is I'm the only one that knows
where as with try and find out how my talk
talk now you want me to have told you
are who you have funny you wouldn't
listen to me before not even for
a minute I know you want me to talk about
something Molly let me alone I know what
I'm saying I was
a silly why didn't you listen to me why
cars are you going out and I already said
when you want to know for so you can write
some more lives so you can sell some
more paper my mind all right all right
I'll tell you what I'll do I'll give you
a story I'll give you whatever story only
this time it'll be trial you know that I
was. Younger somebody and I'm somebody.
She's dead Well she's been
killed she's learning.
How do you see the effort to jump out the
window that when there is no way she's
been dead come to only where you don't
want him he said he's in the desk you can
shoot and kill us what are you doing up
here I can't stand keep quiet you're
sitting pretty Why did they have no you
know what are you doing she said Mrs Bowen
versus Mother what are you doing here I
know. You're doing something wrong I'll
take her out here and what lawyer yes but
I really want to pull out of my climbing
slowly pulling back. Dr Roberts
if she doesn't talk to
a man yes I tell him from the case of ejido
remember something can't write. Well
let go of me. You think you're going I'm
going up to my head I'm going to get Bruce
out of jail well enough why did you have
to do this to me again Bruce out of jail
how can you worry about
a man who's resting in
a nice quiet police station while this is
going on here with you this is war you
can't just I mean I want to get all that
crap you can just start right over there
on the desk on smeared all over the front
page aliens captured by the morning post
I can just start for you and I gotta find
this doing it now and get now it's really
good you know what you mean
I just thought I'd share
a three hundred sixty five days in the
year one good man how many times you got
a murder I knocked on the desk once in
a lifetime got the whole city by the sea
the pain I know I know I know you know
you've got the brain of a paying gig this
isn't just a story you're covering It's
a revolution this is the greatest yawn in
journalism since Livingstone discovered
Stanley the other way around
oh I don't get technical at
a time like this you realize what you've
done on the you have taken aside this
program for about forty years of the same
old game with this yarn you're kicking
them out to give us
a chance to have the same kind of government
your standing under the Guardia listen
I if I didn't have your best interests at
heart you think I waste my time arguing
with you have done something big
deal to your step down into
a new clients will make sense monkeys out
of those War He lives next Tuesday nobody
over I'm not even there why
expose it may certainly be
a crucial find out more we keep Williams
on the cover until morning till the post
can break the story exclusive then with
the governor in on the capture share the
glory with it I guess you could go
with all city hall I'm going to have
a god come to me and I will back up again
so will you but one. This race not even I
want to name this is just a
newspaper story you know that it's
a career and you stand there bellyaching
about when you got to make talk to your
nine o'clock trying to
figure out how to lay off
a steak that's why even though I had full
I feel they've been in the streets if you
will the Johnson Street they'll be statues
if I go movies I've got you know radio
by tomorrow morning I'll bet you have
a Woody Johnson Guard see the
billboards now is it lined up with was
a lot of money not that we got to do it all
again you can we can sit here and tell
you one of my private off it off
phone him how are you going to take
a seat you know that he designed the Deseret
carry the desk over oh you can't move
that desk is calling the cops how far I
were large out the window with police not
quick start to get the time line over here
come on stop fighting I believe this is
stuff you want otherwise you go along to
me what can I call it had better pray
coming a much time and how
kind about if I did have
a different word I would tell her you can't
say because the biggest story in years
verily I was captured by the Morning Post
expose it yet and I want to tell the
whole front page that's one example from
page out never mind the European war we
got something
a lot bigger than mad dogs right now need
are going to see finished and Listen
dummy can hold a bunch of product
I'm going to write I have
a dozen of his wrestlers Yeah but I'll
probably have one but I'm going to describe
him I'm only what the deuce do you want
I'll break your leg No no never mind the
Chinese are quite friends really I just
want to ask you one question is how did you
get out of jail not through any Hell no
you're going buddy you're going to my way
of me like I had
a wire already for one hundred dollars so
I can get out on bail No I don't care if
there's
a million big I don't know what they're
going to think up there in Albany they hit
send the money to the police station all
for Pete's sake here we come all the way
but I story I would explain everything to
the little I was Mother she said she was
coming up I see that I can hear nothing
what if you go outside to play fella no
junk no polish card really tell me where
my mother was go ahead if you couldn't say
on their mind that this is more people get
the money from her now if you know now
right I'll take that money till I raise
my game I start and I can manage things
around here I'll take that sort of all
your extra I'll give it to you Bruce here
you know if you'll find your my in the
wallet my wallet this is my wallet say
something. Money going out to what you're
doing just want to look at it. Really I'm
glad I go right to we are taking the nine
o'clock oh I don't care what I said I
said I'm taking on I black all blue
Is that what it. That alone when
your buddy when you do the paper for the
real you just want to that's what you want
to wear something you don't want to come
forward because that was really your dog
do it no thank all of
Miss America printed off
a film to tell me please tell me the truth.
I don't want to be you know you and I
look here my good man you showed up or not
how can I never think you're wrong all
was right all right she wanted to get away
from everything you stand for but you
were too such a partner and changed
your mind take a lie and stick him on
a funny page let me ask you
if you want to have it for
a man like him now I am not the press can't
see that something happened wait I'll
tell you every time you tell him no he's
a spy you're full no you're not to come
on here you're coming with me right now
give me just
a second chance you don't see is the
biggest thing in my why I see I'll keep my
something in the ice box on the air just
don't love I'll do that and I know just
because of all this news that I don't love
you and I know that isn't the point you
are one of the boys you should never
intended to be decent to live like
a human being which are all right all right
you want something that is pure and I
tell you when you are trying to come to
dislike him and all are ready to let your
last one I have NO NO need the rest and
tell me alone that human interest if you
get hold of what you're going to put your
understanding of I don't I understand all
right I don't dislike them it is only
one question I want to know what
a swell it by the mass first wife was the
name I mean the woman I want on it I
Fanny when you say I believe
I think you know love me
a little Never mind I don't know where
you're from and the time you're going to
change your mind I'm leaving on the mind
of claptrap all along that instead of
trying to do something else I'm just
didn't think you'd just take from the sky
realty keep it from your face and you can't
get back either way you mock turtle.
Island Duffy did it don't was just
going to dig a Daisy was a man or
a living dead good stay on this wire which
is on his way over all do was hold on
for fifteen minutes pointed back to
coming in here to phone. Down the Moon.
Find three guesses made over yet all you
know you got enough. So the British. Are
going on the line I guess that's where
groups whose only one is kind I can't
understand why did you want to go so far
let me here while hundreds of share
hotlines paid government stops in the city
shooting innocent bystanders spreading
their reign of terror over it is looking
less than twenty am I right and I'm going
to make the post was in the paper got the
quote I did it right then the second
paragraph going to read the second paragraph
there's no need for ten years I've
been telling you how to write
a newspaper story that's when I get
I'm sorry. About the audio I have
no are present OK task all of.
This what you say is name
of you think I'm trying to be. I
mean any better sense in that
hello hello Mr Varian I'm not having you
come over here come up and again oh you
know my. Excuse me I just want to get my
own you know you know it's going to go and
see you tonight isn't it yes
you know how do you mean as
a matter of fact I was talking to Mr Duffy
about you just this afternoon really
well and I think that
a mental On the contrary on the contrary
that was once where the story had an
effect of the smallest Oh did you did you
care for the poem Mr Bird and the poem
The poem was great I like the ending
especially when I was well outside itself but
in his heart he has the hangman calling
and the gallows following and his wife
married mothers to. Heartbreaking that's
fine I'm going to work for me well yes we
can use
a man like you know what we've got now and
I was over I was like John to me Are you
serious with
a very dubious lying to. Me I'm sending me
sometimes you want to say you have been
singing American There's no yeah no Roy
you write me wrong I ve been you know the
poet when I've gone as you would know
you probably never heard of Shakespeare
either I think. I'll go and see the book
depending on the stuff right away I'm not
getting on the Tribune Right now seventy
five I'm going to know by nine you'll give
him everything you want to understand OK
I'm not going to play I want to write me
a story from the point of view of this
great man the high conquering afraid of
every sound of every light years footsteps
is how it's going I got all the time
they're coming and I get the sense
that the animal had been a sort of
a Jack London style bank rate I'll just
get my writing ticket don't have to grind
don't have to run home I'm
deeply grateful I'm just
a very you know it's very Yet oh oh
if you should have an opening for
a war correspondent I probably
a little French you know
I keep in mind. That
is why did mothers feel when I listen to
them from advancing years down the road to
say you're right no and when we came out
of the word driving Barbara we don't want
to just tell them alone until the extras
are going to let me get them does stare
tell crossings Well you
said it didn't teach him
a lesson he won't quit his paper without
giving notice I mean you may have
a cross anybody would like to know well I
just remembered it isn't coming back you
said you're taking
a lot of talk to all want to not go she's
gone by now come on are always arriving
get out of the story you don't have
a right to offer me for the full experience
you know you have messed up my life
what am I going to do the windows too small
to carry the desk out of that building
right now I want my I'm falling for you
all and I got a name streets after
a generous Yes well you had
a nice restaurant got to make don't
actually require much. Oh is it me blasted
really really. Holy smokes what about him
I just bought like you do with I haven't
been
a five dollars he was going sixty five miles
an hour you know what I mean take that
mush out of him Well you know
lady tell me when so I can do
a police patrol you know what I mean we
busted in head I see her don't worry she
tell me you imagine bumping into
a lot of cops they come rolling
out like aren't trying to do with
a switch me when I come to I was one of got
Don't you want to write you was on your
in the taxi cab driver
got knocked cold but
a finger is crying you know Dana thinks I'm
going to hand over the company I had or
the cops was on the wrong side of history
and now everything's fine she's probably
squawking your head off in the police I
don't think she's quite good much you know
what I mean don't tell me she killed me
why she did you notice me say listen me
when I got on the hip and I kidnapped
old lady on my hands I'm going to stick
around asking questions from a
lot of cops you know what I'm
a good dad all this yeah all. Right Hilda
you what will be will be I'm not going to
say to Bruce OK Tell him or Tommy if he
really loves you you won't have to tell him
anything snap out of it would you rather
have the old dame dragging the whole
police force in and I killed him I'm
just. Am I going to do how can I have
a face Bruce again look at me I am looking
at you you'll notice it was my own
grandmother I'd carry on you know I would
for the paper the way that happened.
Before I got credit we could do
more you know become less and.
Less like making five seven zero zero
zero but why are you Alice not going to
receive one please well what are you
doing there and you even starting about
healing jobs I wasn't only writing them
from another classic Sebastien budget
listen it's
a matter of life and death nobody can hear
mornings I don't know if it's now time
to speak up I want when you can't stop for
a day now I will community are going to be
receiving my I don't have even after six
years but you're all my good
steak you're going to let
a woman got me doing this after all we've
been through don't actually Johnson was
there no lady wrote in their notes national
bunch I broke my arm if I'm for you up
to here now you can double cross me I look
around like he does oh I put her on I'll
talk to her Oh Good evening madam Now listen
you're tensing Grammar Girl you can't
keep you away from his duty one time he
was saying that again I'll come over and
kick you in that teeth So Mary what kind
of language is that no no do you. Keep on
not what did I say. That right I know I
got most I was something I got right yes
I'm gonna hear that Ari it's cooperate All
right that's right well way every guy
play. Silence I know better than I or
anybody with a disease I'm going to be
a two one knowing when. Yes But
no you don't you need to use
a bodyguard get all the same guys you want
anybody with hair on his chest get him
off the street get him anywhere off from
anything all together we've got to get
that discount against him but there's an
important lesson go you know the best
friend I got I like you don't fail me get
enough people to move that desk I want
every lawyer you know me was to shine off
my back carry don't bump into anything.
That dumb immigrant reassures young boy I
am hospitals that are out of your bag and
five is going to carry it out
alone you anything you want as
a million ways we start
a fire at the farm and take it
on the confusion I don't give
a damn what you do you come here so we
can lift up our children oh never mind
you're going to make them no I'm not if
you want to strain my back I'm going to
find is all of. Them are going to.
Be what I am right now I am what I
write I'm
a lawyer you off me now look here John
somehow you mean me yes you do what do you
mean by breaking in here like this. You
can't bluff me Burns I don't care who you
are what paper you read and all that go and
they were not I was please look for my
son is happening my mother I want to hear
you I mean if you want to get Williams at
the door my and I were in there talking I
know where he is all the kind of anything
really in this been an accident John said
there's something very very peculiar
going on here and I'll see here just
a moment I well if you have any accusations
to make make them in the proper manner
otherwise I'll have to ask you to get
out you ask me what. Oh you will
a you keep that door closed Don't let anybody
in or out now we'll see about this on
thank you in the third degree have them
talk and you've got Williams But yes now
look here Johnson I'm going to get to the
bottom of this are you going to talk
around to me to say what do you know about
William what you know about way and now
we're getting it all right boys take her
out of here I was away on her tongue can't
touch me and. She got that.
All right I'll take that gun.
Where did you get this stuff out of my
carry on if I want to know this guy I
explained that I well when he told me he
was going to interview world Williams is
going to be dangerous or give
a gun to defend us all you did well that's
very interesting but this happens to be
the gun that Williams used
to shoot his way out with
a good man you're trying to make me out
a liar I often on my own gun or not
that's where you got it and I got it from
Williams Where is there with him where you
got him you're barking up the wrong tree
Ah well I'll give you three minutes to tell
me where he is but out of the hospital
to call
a professor at the bank marshmallow Where
is he asked the master mind what he's
doing here speak up speak up what do you
know about this fellow Where is the
Morning Post does not obstruct justice saw
I had criminal you ought to know that
Johnson you were under arrest and you to
burn so I was under arrest listen you in
significant Square told him boy and it's
find you realize what you're doing I'll
show you what I'm doing during your
obstructing justice and so I was the Morning
Post and I'm going to see that you're fined
ten thousand dollars you'll see nothing
like I'm going to begin by impounding the
post property is this your desk now days
what are you afraid of you know the idea
to move this day has got to go yes go
ahead and try all right I will I want to
you move this kind of this building and
I'll put you behind bars that you would
kill is that so often the Roosevelt hears
about I tell him Come on boys All right
stay on the stand your last chance this is
a federal offense and you'll
find any accessory or take
a chance on that Go Ahead boys. Own
up this girl mother your mother
I am glad to see I all right I mean I got
in and they get it right there. What's
the idea here this lady trade she's been
kidnapped why they dragged me all the way
down the stairs and would just let this man
have anything to do with it when he was
in charge of the whole thing he told them
to kidnap me Excuse me madam are you
referring to me you know you did what about
these mines kidnapping and Jonna free
me I never saw this woman before in my life
why what is thing to say I was standing
right here when that girl tells how the
economy are going to come here right away
look here madam be honest if you were
joyriding placid or got into some scrape Why
don't you admit it instead of accusing
innocent people around here how can you talk
that you can be just
a little crazy mother and I get you something
more and I can tell you why they did
yeah that's some kind of
a murderer in here and they were hiding
and I don't know yet here YOU ARE OUR
a liar and you know it. Was
that because in the next.
Ten back everybody how do you make sure
that your guns on his home is don't take
any chances shoot right through that it
had about you got his gun here on on your
grave you know you really came to that.
Road that all the way or you know what I
would take hang on and he called up or you
know you don't want to say a skunk in
a minute now everybody all the way the
Senate and let it all right our frank want
to get on each end of the next coming up
we've got you covered we're going to have
it in
a minute don't try to move any time I come
free time why I'm ready for an emergency
who any second now three up and I got to
we're going to go ahead and shoot me I'm
sure we were best kept in the classroom
in the criminal courts building having
a desk come around your people have always
been trying to funny stuff but it was
unconscious when they were
on the desk with us put up
a desperate struggle to please our party
offered no resistance might show up with
a cop for the gun work breakthrough according
to police every morning for me that
turned Williams over to the sheriff what
the cops on these people made of us not
receive a show like one
and capture all. Share
a strange and mysterious I won't always
get away with it was I think what I still
like you know she went. Back to.
And I mean even the warden's office quote
I well you're going to wish you never
been born or am I. Pray for our final work
week just certain to deliver the goods
I'm proud of you know kind of natural don't
fight for Sarai to get escape criminal
and
a little charge of kidnapping at my second
meeting and that's the jail Mr Simon Al
looks like about ten years apiece for you
to bird is it and everything you've got
the Morning Post like this time for you to
get out of town questioning in the dark
but I'm not happy this time your job is
the last man who said that to me was on
T.V. Just
a week before he got this is Rob So we've
been there was James Lewis and wielded.
You forget the power that always watches
over the Morning Post my line either way
and I love this is heartless I have caught
him yeah swimmers same go I am going
proceed to the hanging purse cage you are
going to be in office exactly two days
more like I was happening and I would have
to tell you that I was I tell you what
you'll be doing was you'll be gone
make up and making rooms in the state
penitentiary Hello Joe is this what I want
you to come over to my office right away
yes I just captured
a couple of important birds and I want
you to take the confession out of
a gun they've always are and I are not
going to help you and I know this and you
are talking to them only Both are the
pressure I'm listening to your men and you
are found I want the power of the press is
President peña his reprise of shade your
he said get out of here you can't drive me
my wife out of here you'll know I won't
Here's the repairing I don't want to be
your city so you know what I want but I'm
out for a night out
you're just a minute wait
a minute who's trying to drive you they
wouldn't take this he should say what did I
tell ya and I'm seeing her what do
you mean by coming in here with
a current war story like that very much
he's an imposter arrested comes after
minute trying to hand man women lection
and that's murder that's allowed ever saw
him before who promised to tell him I want
your name the penny bone jumping point
if you deliver this first missed if anybody
talked to they started right and right
because they close yeah that's for sure
and I'm a face of a lover is talking like
a child out of the mouths of babes I'll
behave the same comic or something why
after some fortunate man Williams has
really been reprieved I personally took no
definite you'll be on the line you hang
your own mother to be reelected I don't
know our whole thing to say about anybody
Miss JOHNSON Oh you have my was take
a look at your water you're an intelligent
man by that time of your story Mr Penny
BO Well I think years ago I'm writing this
is pretty good all that while she was
Miss Page going Oh if she was one of them
I mean Jones sheriff this document is
authentic and our winners have been reprieved
and our commonwealth has been saved
to pay for the specialty of shedding blood
ferret our Get off the soapbox I don't
want to turn you take those handcuffs off
which I'm going to I'm amazed that you're
doing
a thing like they offered water. Not badly
I feel no excuse an offer to fly off the
handle I was only doing my duty nothing
personal that's what you're saying and I
want to tell you Paul was yes
here's a picture of my wife
a fine looking woman who you haven't seen
or you know we should all right although
she's good enough for me if I was to tell
mine I am going to Mr Freddy phone and as
long as I'm mayor why I have to be
about three more hours I had sat
a long enough for us to get out special
edition asking for your recall and your
eyes you know your little boys ought to
get about ten years apiece and I think
after don't make any hasty decisions Mr
Burns you might run into with something big
libel So you're going to run into the
government my old friend the governor and I
understand each other perfectly
Yes and so do I charge you
a watch Odo and I was depended on of
your come on our last word take over the
waters office and deliver this trip brave
come along Pete Rouse you know why why
you want to after. What it was to future
jailbirds we want to post makes clear he's
not to be up against the
West Ham we've been in
a long time well I'm wary as I get him
and then at the time we still own
a leg of the stomach off the contest this
isn't in my office any time you need
those guys never let me proceed being
poisoned the old year and hide after
a week during the day so who tell that
that's where I mean how we are going to jail
over there do you know that yes maybe
you're right you know that it's
a bad business you're going to be better
off so you better get going right now with
a bruise that goes. You know he's going
to get to and I'll just send him
a wire you'll be waiting at the station
when you get annoyed when I go on I don't
know why didn't i Phone But you know maybe
he's going oh there you go again what is
that with you wait
a minute I know kind of can't you understand
I'm trying to do something noble for
once in my life I get out of you before I
change for my color is tough enough now
just a minute send
a fellow why Anyway when you get in I don't
know who write the story I do it myself
and we have because you don't want to get
my story I kind of like to think that I
like Oh I'd laugh I get all of the same
old act isn't it kind of pushed me out of
here thinking I'll be stupid enough to want
to stay Oh I know I deserve that early
but I'm
a golfer but this is one time you're wrong
but honey when you walk out the door
part of me will go right with you but
a whole new world going to open up for you
I made fun of Bruce nobody you know like
I said you know why I was jealous I was
sore because he can offer you the kind of
life I can give you I think you're one and
i am i could stay do the story and take
the train the morning I think at some point
somebody Good bye dear and good luck.
And I was going to go so far. Just
a minute. Oh no he doesn't know it's
just left I'm still here I can take
any of them and he'll just making
a fourth priest or Playstation I'll put
them on as I try your way all the way
for far for having counterfeit
money I think many hold on
a minute duffing all right if
you get it I can't. Right now
I'm just.
Really. Really. Really Don't don't
cry please. Come on I did mean every
time you looked him over you never cried
Bissell. You know they like to send me
away. I don't know yet I'm like to.
Hear on the level the ones that you would
just stand behind me go off when the
underling a thing about.
You Why do you think I was
a chump and I think you did.
What you think you. Know.
What it is to go out for rehab to get them
out of jail simply down to some honest
money and company were able to.
Make everything change telling
you to stand by we're coming in the office
now don't worry about the story and he's
going to write it because she's not quite
He's never did you know we're going to
get married that you can't think.
You can be amazing at this
No no not just for the Do we really. Want
I don't know where we're going we're
going to Niagara Falls Niagara Falls dummy
two weeks will show you burned it but.
I'm strike might strike where
Albany I know is on the
way down but I really did I did OK Duffy.
But he's never grazed as we go over the I
want to push computers up take that U.K. .